# VONJAE HWANG

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

wnjhwng@gmail.com wonjaehwang.com (408) 455 - 0301 in /wonjaehwang verydecent

### SUMMARY

Full stack web developer transitioning from 5+ years of experience in the customer service industry. A deeply curious coder intrigued by the various elements of successful product development and business management. Enthusiastic about working in team environments and values learning from team members through collaboration.

### SKILLS

Javascript, React.js, Node.js, Python, HTML, CSS

# **PROJECTS**

Lambda School Labs - Chattr, Real time Customer Service Platform

Feb. 2019 - Mar. 2019

- Deployed a month long project on a 4 developer team.
- Created app using Socket.io, React.js, Node.js.
- Oversaw research and implementation of Socket.io between the server and client side, developing front end functionalities.

# **EMPLOYMENT**

#### Mizu Sushi Bar & Grill, Server, San Jose, CA

Aug. 2014 - Mar. 2015, Mar. 2017 - Feb. 2018

- Communicated with 8+ coworkers to complete prep work for service.
- Served large parties (16+), assigned tasks to teammates based on environment conditions.
- Multitasked order taking, order processing 5+ different customers and delivered orders in timely manner.

#### Sushi Garden, Server, Scotts Valley, CA

Nov. 2016 - Jan. 2017

- Awarded employee of the month for receiving restaurant's first 5 star Yelp review for efficient and courteous service.
- Calculated daily income and distributed tips amongst 3-4 servers.

# **EDUCATION**

Lambda School June 2018 - Mar. 2019

- Attended live lectures every weekday morning learning web development and computer science lessons.
- Daily stand ups with Project Manager to review lesson concepts and solve any blockers.
- Completed one project every week for 7 months based on the following topics: Version control, HTML, CSS, Responsive design, Javascript, React, Node, HTTP, API design, SQL, Relational Databases, Python, C, Data Structures, Algorithms, Basic Computer Science theories.
- Managed and guided team of students during Build Week as Scrum Master, to create tip sending app in the service industry.
- Completed the Labs program, a one month project with 5 developers creating a live chat customer service platform.

JobTrain Sept. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- 3 month web technology school to learning the Salesforce Administrator CRM and practices for professional development
- Presented final salesforce project to employees at Box
- Practiced live interview with Jobvite recruiter